hystersisters.com 2010-11-20

# Hyster Sisters Privacy Policy - HysterSisters.com

We respect your privacy!

Any personal information you give to the HysterSisters website (the Website) will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. Personal information is information about a person that includes identifying information about that person.

***We do not actively submit pages with usernames to search engines, but they are picked up by a number of them. If you have a username that is your actual full name, it may be possible to search for your name and find it affiliated with HysterSisters. This is why, during registration, we warn members *not* to register with an identifiable username. We have no control over search engine results.

Revisions to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy as necessary. If we change this Privacy Policy then it will be updated accordingly here on this Website. We recommend that you review this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are aware of any changes.

Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:

The HysterSisters Website does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including email lists.

Research

HysterSisters does occasionally engage in research initiatives related to women's health. The sole purpose of these research initiatives is to identify unmet needs of women through aggregate reporting of women's experiences, opinions and therapeutic treatments.

Research is typically conducted through opt-in survey where survey response data is summarized, reported in the aggregate and made available for purchase to various constituents in the medical community who need to hear the voice of women. These constituents include, but are not limited to: doctors, hospitals and pharmaceutical manufacturers and distributors.

In addition to research conducted from opt-in survey response data, textural data you provide in your posts may be summarized and reported at a non-personal, aggregate level on a periodic basis for the purpose of identifying trends in consumer education and opinion.

Neither of the aforementioned forms of data collection for research purposes retain or report on any personal information.

Browser information collected on the Website:

The HysterSisters Website analyzes our Website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on the Website. Our Website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.

Privacy of our email lists:

The HysterSisters Website maintains an email list to keep HysterSisters members informed about breaking events. Members select to be updated via email by the administration of HysterSisters during registration. Checking "no" to "receiving email from admin" in your member's control panel will opt you out of receiving newsletter emails from this site. In addition, we configure our message board software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our members to anyone.

Advertising Policy on HysterSisters:

Please visit this page to read information about HysterSisters Advertising Policy: [[Click here]](http://www.hystersisters.com/vb2/view_advertising.htm).

Database Content

The HysterSisters website is created around a database containing posts, registration info, survey results, private messages, logged IPs and other activities. The information contained within the database belongs to Hyster Sisters, Inc. An administrator of Hyster Sisters, Inc, if so inclined, can access information in the database. Posts, IPs, private messages are all accessible within the database. They are private, but not necessarily secret.

The information you provide in your posts may be summarized at a non-personal level on occasion. See our Research Policy above for more information.

Your identity

HysterSisters.com is a public website. The HysterSisters Website takes precaution in helping you to maintain your privacy within the membership. Although your email address is verified as you join, the email addresses are hidden and are not viewable by members.

We ask that you are careful that you do not provide your email address nor your exact location in order to maintain safety while you use the HysterSisters Website. Although Zip Codes are collected for use in the database for local news emails, they are not displayed publicly. Be safe! Be smart! Do not give your phone number, address, hospital, and other personal info in public forums.

Your identity and Legal Issues

The HysterSisters Website retains the right to provide any information we know about you to legal authorities in the event of legal action arising from your online activity.

Updating or Changing Your Information

HysterSisters wants your account , information and preferences to be accurate and complete. To update or change your personal information, visit our user login page and log on to your own account. You can update your personal information after logging in to your account.

Use of Cookies and Other Technologies

The Website may use cookies to enhance your experience while using the Website. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that site and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Website will not function properly when you view them.

The Website also may use other technologies to track the specific pages viewed by visitors on the Website or to target specific content that might be of interest to you. These technologies help us to understand how visitors use the Website. However, you will have the option to opt out (or opt on if applicable law requires) of receiving such targeted content on those pages of our Website where this technology is used.

Log Files

Other information passively collected by HysterSisters is in the form of logs – files that record Website activity and gather statistics about web users' browsing habits. These entries are generated anonymously, and help HysterSisters determine (among other things) how many and how often users have visited our Website, which pages they've visited, and other similar data. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you. Log files are used internally only, and are not associated with any particular user, computer, or browser.

Linking to Third Party Sites

To provide relevant information not found on our Website and to facilitate online shopping, HysterSisters may provide links from our Website to third party websites. HysterSisters encourages our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information.

Online Store

Visitors purchasing goods and services through the HysterSisters online store will need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address in our safe, secured, encrypted online environment. The credit card information is used for the moment of transaction only and not saved in a customer account NOR saved to the server’s database.

The Website is Not For Children

Since the Website is not designed specifically for children, HysterSisters does not intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a person under the age of 13, we will automatically delete it.

California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:  
HysterSisters  
2436 S. I-35 E. Suite 376-184  
Denton, Texas 76205 

What constitutes my acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using the Website, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effective date of any modification to the Privacy Policy will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms. 

HysterSisters Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect via the Internet. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information in any way and at any time without your prior knowledge and permission. If you have questions about the privacy procedures employed at HysterSisters, please contact:  
HysterSisters  
2436 S. I-35 E. Suite 376-184  
Denton, Texas 76205

_The effective date of this Privacy Policy is July 1, 2009. This Website is intended for viewing within the United States._

Page Created at 06-08-2003 - 07:00 AM, Last Modified 07-10-2009 - 07:50 AM 

---|---|---
